[{"answer": "I don't think we'll go to war.  We shouldn't even be here.  This isn't our fight, it's a regional conflict.  It should be decided regionally", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "People were suffering in that place, and we didn't do anything", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm just trying to help you guys out.  It doesn't hurt to know something about that place", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I didn't learn Arabic because we were getting shipped here.  You don't learn it in a couple of weeks.  I studied it in high school", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What does that mean", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How do you say", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Naw, nothing", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'll show my friend.  He'll be sorry when I get this thing open", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What's your point, my friend?  You have a point", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It doesn't mean anything", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "A map?  All I got is maps.  I'm gonna have Delayed Map Syndrome when I finally get out of here.  What kind of map you need?  Topographical, geographical, thermal", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "A map map", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Some good ones", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend's got a boil on his ass", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "They finally start the ground war, and where are we?  Same place we've been since we got here.  Securing freedom for the dirt", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'd like to go home alive with a couple of Iraqi scalps hanging from my belt", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Third.  What you're going to do with your third", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "A car?  You're going to buy a car", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " We have to go back", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " We just about got killed.  You know what happened?  We just about got killed, and you want to go on", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh, God!  Oh God", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It's a mine, isn't it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why you got to move away to talk!", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You're moving away because it's going to blow up, isn't it!?  It's going to blow up", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What are we going to do?  What the hell are we going to do", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " They're going to kill us", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What are you doing", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It looks like you're not doing anything", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It'll be too dark to make our way back now.  Let's bed down for the night and head out at first light", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What about it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I told you.  He tried to steal our gold. He tried to kill us", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "He's a soldier.  He doesn't need a weapon.  He's got rocks.  He's got bare hands", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " We can't just leave him.  He'll run back to his outfit, report our position..", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "That's what he says.  He could be a spy, or something", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "That's what he says.  He could be a spy, or something", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You don't know he isn't", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Tell me something, my friend.  Are you crazy, greedy, or just stupid?  my friend says you're crazy", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Me?  I say you don't have enough brains to be stupid", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You lie in the middle of the road, look like you're hurt.  When the car stops I run over to the driver and put a gun to his head", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Somebody has to", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I'm thinking about taking a trip", "docId": "Three-Kings-(Spoils-of-War).txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Still am.  There's more gold than I thought, and since there's only two of us now...  Where should I go", "qsentId": 42}]